(upbeat music)
♪ Hey, hey ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey ♪
♪ Simmer down, simmer down ♪
♪ They say we're too young now
to amount to anything else ♪
♪ But look around ♪
♪ We worked too damn hard for
this just to give it up now ♪
♪ If you don't swim, you'll drown ♪
♪ But don't move, honey ♪
♪ You look so perfect standing there ♪
♪ In my American Apparel underwear ♪
♪ And I know now that I'm so down ♪
♪ Your lipstick stain is a work of art ♪
♪ I got your name tattooed
in an arrow heart ♪
♪ And I know now that I'm so down, hey ♪
♪ Hey, hey ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey ♪
♪ Let's get out, let's get out ♪
♪ 'Cause this deadbeat town's
only here just to keep us down ♪
♪ While I was out ♪
♪ I found myself alone, just thinkin' ♪
♪ If I showed up with a plane ticket ♪
♪ And a shiny diamond ring
with your name on it ♪
♪ Would you wanna run away too ♪
♪ 'Cause all I really want is you ♪
♪ You look so perfect standing there ♪
♪ In my American Apparel underwear ♪
♪ And I know now that I'm so down ♪
♪ I made a mixed tape
straight out of '94 ♪
♪ I've got your ripped skinny
jeans lying on the floor ♪
♪ And I know now that I'm so down, hey ♪
♪ Hey, hey ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey ♪
♪ You look so perfect standing there ♪
♪ In my American Apparel underwear ♪
♪ And I know now that I'm so down ♪
♪ Your lipstick stain is a work of art ♪
♪ I got your name tattooed
in an arrow heart ♪
♪ And I know now that I'm so down, hey ♪
♪ Hey, hey ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey ♪
♪ You look so perfect standing there ♪
♪ In my American Apparel underwear ♪
♪ And I know now that I'm so down, hey ♪
♪ Your lipstick stain
is a work of art, hey ♪
♪ I got your name tattooed
in an arrow heart, hey ♪
♪ And I know now, hey,
that I'm so down, hey ♪
(tape whirring)